<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt>
    <head>
        <styling>
        </styling>
    </head>
    <body>
        <div xml:lang="en">
            <p begin="10">Hi, I'm Tanvi.  I'm a technology analyst.  
</p>
<p begin="13">I work as an application developer within Global Rates and Currencies Technology at Bank of America.  
</p>
<p begin="19" end="25">On a day-to-day basis, I'm involved in writing and maintaining software for financial risk management.  
</p>
<p begin="29">I would definitely recommend a summer internship at                    Bank of America.
</p> 
<p begin="32">If you're serious about working in the financial services industry,      Bank of America would be the best place to do your internship.   
</p>
<p begin="39" end="46">Within the nine weeks you will be exposed to several different sides  of the bank and at the end of it you would be in a very good position to make a decision.  
</p>
<p begin="50">Coming into work in the financial services industries means that I need to have a strong knowledge base of global markets and investment banking.  
</p>
<p begin="58" end="63">So, combining that with learning about technology has been quite challenging.
</p>
<p begin="67">The bank will support all forms of career development activities that you want to explore, whether it's learning about technology, 
</p>
<p begin="75">whether it's learning about the business side of things, whether it's     soft skills you're interested in.  We have courses and affinity groups for each and every activity that's out there.
</p>
<p begin="85">I'm involved in the Women in Technology and Operations and the Multicultural Leadership Network here at Bank of America.  We meet regularly for dinner, for networking.  
</p>
<p begin="94" end="101">And we talk about what everyone's been up to in their stream of work and what are the new and interesting things they're getting involved in. 
</p>
<p begin="107">You should come and work for Bank of America because of the  cultural diversity here.  No matter which part of the world you're from there is a place for you here.  
</p>
<p begin="114" end="121">Your opinions will be heard.  You will be able to make your voice heard and you will be rewarded accordingly for your input.  

</p>
        </div>
    </body>
</tt>
