<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt>
	<head>
		<styling>
		</styling>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div xml:lang="en">
<p begin="10">My name is Anton and I am a Project Manager within Human Resources.
</p>
<p begin="14">Human resources really deals with working with people and that is everything from recruitment - so, getting them into the door, to developing them once they're inside and  
</p>
<p begin="23" end="30">making sure that there is a bright and vibrant culture, making sure people are paid correctly, that they're incentivized correctly.
</p>
<p begin="33">My job here at the bank really consists of
</p>
<p begin="37">taking a problem that someone has and really working to understand why they're having the problem then moving to find a solution for them.  
</p>
<p begin="46" end="52">And then once we come up with a solution to their problem, we then work to make that happen.  		
</p>
<p begin="55" end="66">Bank of America does a great job of offering different avenues for people to get connected and different ways for people to meet up within Charlotte, or across the bank, or across the globe. 
</p>
<p begin="68">When I'm not in the office, I really like to try to get out and explore Charlotte.  
</p>
<p begin="74">It's a really fun city, it's a really young city, and it's a fun city to kind of get around and explore different pockets of culture that you have here.
</p>
<p begin="82">I'm also involved in a couple of different community service activities with my fraternity, Alpha Phi Alpha Fraternity Incorporated.  
</p>
<p begin="89" end="97">We do a mentorship program for young high school seniors, and at the end of it we present them with a scholarship to help them go and pay for college. 
</p>
<p begin="101">My first advice to anybody who is looking to come into the bank, or any company for that matter, is to understand what your passion is.  
</p>
<p begin="109">For a new graduate who is looking at employment and wondering 'Where should I go?' and 'What should I do?' I would say really look at the people who are inside the company; look at what the company is doing as a whole.  
</p>
<p begin="120">Is the company being progressive, is the company pushing itself?  Are you going to learn within that company?  And that's something<br>
 you can only get by talking to people who actually work inside that company.  
</p>
<p begin="131">And if that's the place that you want to go, and you feel like you can learn and grow and develop to pursue your passion and to meet your goals, then I would say that's the place you want to be.  
</p>
<p begin="138" end="140">And for me that was Bank of America. 
</p>
			

		</div>    
	</body>
</tt>