<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt>
	<head>
		<styling>
		</styling>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div xml:lang="en">
<p begin="10">Hi.  My name is Kaitlyn.  I'm a first-year analyst in Equity Specialist Sales. 
</p>
<p begin="14">So I'm essentially a stockbroker to institutional clients.  And those clients are hedge funds, mutual funds and pension fund managers.  
</p>
<p begin="20" end="28">So we provide our clients with both stocks that they can physically buy and sell, but also the research ideas behind those stocks. 
</p>	
<p begin="32">When I come in in the morning, the most important part of our job is getting information to our clients before the market opens.  
</p>
<p begin="38" end="42">So I like to get in early, read our research and help prepare it for our clients so that they can be prepared when they get in, in the morning. 
</p>
<p begin="46">The most challenging part of my job, I’d have to say, is pitching stocks to clients.  Some of my clients are very sophisticated.  
</p>
<p begin="52">They’ve been in this business for longer than I’ve been alive.  And I have to gather the confidence and the industry knowledge to be able to pitch them the stock. 
</p>
<p begin="59" end="62">So while it is the most difficult part of my job, it’s also the most exciting.		
</p>
<p begin="66">I interned for the bank in the summer of 2009.  It was great because of a rotational program.   
</p>
<p begin="70" end="79">I got to spend time in three very different parts of the bank from equity sales to structured products trading to short-term fixed income. 
</p>
<p begin="82">I was pleasantly surprised that from an early stage the bank gives you a lot of responsibility.  
</p>
<p begin="87">For my day-to-day work, I'm already involved in real client interaction and revenue generating activities.  
</p>
<p begin="93">The first time I walked into a Bank of America Merrill Lynch trading floor, there was something different about it.   
</p>
<p begin="98">I had been on other trading floors before and I really think the difference had to do with the people.   
</p>
<p begin="103">I could see a sense of enthusiasm and passion in these people and when I started meeting them, talking to them, that same enthusiasm was instantly instilled in me. 
</p>
<p begin="111">I've been playing sports my whole life.  I've played field hockey at college, so, the team atmosphere is something that I really just strive in.
</p>
<p begin="118" end="127">Whether it’s my competitive nature or just team or leadership abilities, the team-work part was a huge aspect of why I came to Bank of America Merrill Lynch.
</p>
<p begin="131">I absolutely love living and working in New York.  I'm going on my five year mark living in the city.    
</p>
<p begin="136" end="146">I mean, as most people would say, there’s always something going on, there’s always people around. Whether you want to go to a small coffee shop, you want to go to a big club, everything that you want to do is offered in New York City. 
</p>
<p begin="151">I really think the best piece of advice I can give is come in and meet us.  I think if you come in and meet the people that you might be working with, you’ll really see if that’s somewhere where you want to work.  
</p>
<p begin="159" end="164">And when I walked into the Bank of America trading floor, I instantly just felt something.  I wanted to work here. 
</p>
			

		</div>    
	</body>
</tt>