<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt>
	<head>
		<styling>
		</styling>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div xml:lang="en">
<p begin="10">Hello, my name is Jarrod.  I’m an Intern for the Applied Technology Program. 
</p>	 
<p begin="14">I’m a full-time student at the University of North Carolina at Charlotte.   
</p>
<p begin="22" end="29">I study Computer Science, and I also have a full-time internship with Bank of America where I work 19 hours a week providing production support for applications that are actually in use by the bank.  
</p>
<p begin="33">In Computer Science we study a lot of databases, programming and different areas like that.   
</p>
<p begin="41" end="51">Inside the internship we’re actually checking the databases to make sure the information is populated and we’re also making sure that these programs that were written for the bank are running properly - in that there are no errors inside of them.  
</p>
<p begin="55" end="66">The best part about my job is that it’s very flexible with my school schedule.  So not only am I allowed to be a full-time student, but I can actually gain real-world experience while going to school.  
</p>
<p begin="71">The opportunities that I saw with Bank of America were that I could virtually live anywhere in the country and still work for the bank.   
</p>
<p begin="81" end="90">Plus, I thought that if I ever decided to change career paths and go more business than technical, I had the opportunity to do that at Bank of America, where as other companies that were smaller might pigeonhole me in just technology. 
</p>
<p begin="94">Bank of America’s culture kind of surprised me.  I thought with a large corporation that you’d just kind of be another number.  However, <br>I feel that I’m a person here at Bank of America.  
</p>
<p begin="103" end="112">I’ve actually met with some senior leadership and they’ve sought input from me that has actually made impacts on the business decisions that they’ve made. 
</p>
<p begin="117">The advice I would give somebody about the opportunities here at Bank of America is that an internship really provides you to understand the bank’s culture.  
</p>
<p begin="125">And by doing so, you can figure out if the bank is the right fit for you.  And if it is the right fit for you, then you can pursue the career opportunities here at the bank.  
</p>
<p begin="134" end="138">That will make you a much better employee and it will make you <br>much happier in your career choices. 
</p>
			

		</div>    
	</body>
</tt>