<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt>
	<head>
		<styling>
		</styling>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div xml:lang="en">
<p begin="10">Hi.  I’m Leonard, and I’m a Treasury Management analyst.
</p>
<p begin="13" end="20">I work for Global Treasury Solutions and we provide working capital and cash management solutions for our clients. 
</p>
<p begin="24">I did a summer internship here a year before I started and it was a great opportunity to learn about the team, the products, and familiarize myself with the company and with our clients.  
</p>
<p begin="35" end="39">And it was one of the main reasons why I actually joined the bank. 
</p>
<p begin="44">Bank of America Merrill Lynch gave me a lot of support in making sure that I understood and really knew the businesses and the products <br>that we’re selling.  
</br></p>
<p begin="53" end="63">So they made sure that we had a lot of these classes, web-based trainings and instructor-led sessions, just to ensure that we are comfortable and knowledgeable about what we’re doing. 
</p>
<p begin="67">My manager has just been a very big influencer in my career.  I’ve tried to take on a lot of what he said to me and he’s given me a lot 
</p>
<p begin="76" end="82">in terms of the way that I approach work - giving me the correct winning mind set and making sure I’m passionate about what I do. 
</p>
<p begin="86">One thing that really attracted me to Bank of America is the core values that they hold.  People here really care and they want to make sure that our clients are comfortable, we’re adding value, and of course you may get recognition for what you do. 
</p>
<p begin="99" end="111">It’s a great feeling knowing that what you do has a contribution to something bigger than yourself in that I’m making contributions to the growth of the Asia-Pacific economy, to the people around me and to our clients. 
</p>
<p begin="116" end="133">I like to play basketball in my free time.  And I feel that a lot of the values that you get from basketball such as team work and at the same time being able to shine as an individual really ties into what you can do here at the bank. 
</p>
<p begin="138" end="148">You should come work for Bank of America Merrill Lynch because they make sure that you have all the opportunities and all the support that you’d need in your career, and also it’s a great platform for you to launch off. 
</p>
			

		</div>    
	</body>
</tt>