<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt>
	<head>
		<styling>
		</styling>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div xml:lang="en">
<p begin="10">Hi, my name is Narinder, I’m a Global Markets Associate. 
</p>
<p begin="13" end="24">Basically I work on a trading desk.  It involves buying low and selling high in simple terms.  And what we exactly trade is options, which is calls and puts.
</p>
<p begin="28">What attracted me to the trading floor was the power I had, the power to take a call, to say “I have to do this”, and then make money out of it. 
</p>
<p begin="37">And it’s a real-time result you get.  If you take a call, the next thing you know you took the right call or wrong call. 
</p>
<p begin="43">It’s so diverse.  The team is so diverse in Bank of America.  In my team we have French people, we have Americans, we have Indians, we have Chinese, we have people from Japan.  
</p>
<p begin="53" end="58">It’s such a diverse team and I like talking to different types of people, making new friends.   
</p>
<p begin="62">There are so many opportunities at the bank.  I mean, if you want to grow in the field you are in to, there are so many opportunities.  
</p>
<p begin="69">But if you wanted to learn something new, say if you are in equities and you want to learn something in fixed income, the door is open for you.  
</p>
<p begin="74">You can go to any trader or you can fix an appointment.  You can go and you can you know.  There are so many people I know who have changed their lines also.  
</p>
<p begin="81" end="87">They went to equities, they went to fixed income or they went to trading, they went to sales.  So, the bank is full of opportunities if you want to go.  
</p>
<p begin="91" end="102">My summer internship was great.  I mean, it was one of the best experiences.  I learned so much.  I made so many new friends.  I knew what I had to do in my future, I mean, if I opted this career. 
</p>
<p begin="106">Hong Kong is a really nice place to live.  I didn’t want to go to New York, I did my internship there.  I was working to be in Asia somewhere at this point of time.  
</p>
<p begin="115" end="120">Because it’s also closer to my home in India so I could take a four-hour flight back and I can go on weekends.  
</p>
<p begin="124">One strong reason I would say somebody should come to <br>Bank of America Merrill Lynch is the responsibility they give.  
</br></p>
<p begin="129">Right from the initial days you’re given so much responsibility that you also feel so confident to do whatever you do, and that’s how you learn.   
</p>
<p begin="136" end="144">I mean, once you’re responsible for something, once you know that you are answerable or accountable for something you are doing, you become much more responsible and that’s how you grow.  
</p>
			

		</div>    
	</body>
</tt>