<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt>
	<head>
		<styling>
		</styling>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div xml:lang="en">
<p begin="00">All parents love their children.  All parents want their children to succeed.  
</p>
<p begin="03">There are no experts.  There are only people who get in there and go to work.
</p>
<p begin="07" end="10">We are living by example, we are actually serving.
</p>
<p begin="17" end="20">The Neighborhood Excellence Initiative is a signature philanthropic program.  
</p>
<p begin="24">NEI is really about funding leadership.  We do it in three ways.  We recognize student leaders, local heroes and neighborhood builders.
</p>
<p begin="28" end="31">They’re folks who are really making a difference in their own communities.
</p>
<p begin="33">The real power of the program comes from the passion of local leaders
</p>
<p begin="35" end="41">to really address what have been intractable problems across the country.
</p>
<p begin="44">Non-profit organizations are crucial to the fabric of every community.
</p>
<p begin="47">In many of these leaders have found they’ve cracked the code to how you turn a neighborhood around.
</p>
<p begin="53">We have two major focuses, education and health.  
</p>
<p begin="57">I really didn’t think school was for me, so I just wanted to get out of the system.  My Mom started getting in the Concillio Program and she started telling me hey, you know can go back to school it’s never too late.
</p>
<p begin="66">I love talking to some of our parents and telling them your son, your daughter can be a principal, can be a mayor, can be a CEO.
</p>
<p begin="74">If your mom believes in you and she’s out there, she doesn’t even know how to speak English, and she’s over here telling you, hey, you know, go back to school - I’m going to these classes just to better you, and it just inspires you a whole lot.  
</p>
<p begin="85">I love school now I am the president of LULAC right now in Collin College.
</p>
<p begin="89" end="101">Students whose parents completed our Basse program graduate from High School at a 90.2% rate and of those 78% go on to post-secondary education.  
</p>
<p begin="103">The local heroes are those individuals who are giving of themselves to make their community a better place.
</p>
<p begin="109">All the work we do is really designed to enhance the quality of life for people who are marginalized.  
</p>
<p begin="118">It’s education support, it’s after-school programs, it is job training.  Just a broad array of programming that we offer to reconnect people who have disconnected by poverty.  
</p>
<p begin="129">The community organizing work that I’ve had the privilege to do has shown me that there are people of good will all across the city when working together can make a powerful difference in the lives of their friends and their community.
</p>
<p begin="143" end="154">Over the course of my life I have tried to invest myself in ways that make life better for others.  I think that is the most worthwhile way that an individual can spend his life.
</p>
<p begin="158">The student leader program really supports the next generation of leaders.
</p>
<p begin="161">These are extraordinary young people.
</p>
<p begin="164">Here at Allen High School we have a tradition called Love Week.  
</p>
<p begin="168">Last year it was for an English teacher here who had Scleroderma and we raised $18,210.
</p>
<p begin="172">This year’s recipient has Leukemia.  So, we are hoping to raise awareness about that as well.  
</p>
<p begin="177">Student leaders receive an eight-week internship at a non-profit as well as a trip to Washington D.C. where they interact with peers from around the country.
</p>
<p begin="180">I think it’s really great that Bank of America is investing their time, money and effort into us.  I think it really shows the vision they have for the future.
</p>
<p begin="192">Almost 3,000 individuals and nearly 600 non-profits have been recognized and directly impacted by NEI.
</p>
<p begin="200">Every one of us have talents and abilities and gifts that can be used to make life better for others.
</p>
<p begin="207">One of the things that makes this country great is how we make a choice to give back.
</p>
<p begin="212" end="217">If a man who is blind can climb Mount Everest, then I can do all I am doing and even more.
</p>

		</div>    
	</body>
</tt>