<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt>
	<head>
		<styling>
		</styling>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div xml:lang="en">
<p begin="10">
Hi, I'm Howard.  I'm an associate in the Global Loans and Special Situations Group.
</p>
<p begin="14">I'm a research analyst here at Bank of America Merrill Lynch.  I cover distressed real estate opportunities, both on the commercial real estate side and home builders.  
</p>
<p begin="22" end="32">I help our traders make markets in those credits and I also spend a lot of my time talking to our clients, mostly hedge funds, about making certain investments in those spaces. 
</p>
<p begin="36">The most challenging part of my job is actually probably the most exciting.  And it's that you really can't predict what's about to happen.  
</p>
<p begin="43">You have to be very flexible because situations change around you very quickly.  
</p>
<p begin="47" end="60">And even those circumstances that may not be very likely, if they happen, you really have to be prepared so that you can support your traders and so that you can support your clients as they make timely investment decisions. 
</p>
<p begin="63">The firm invests very heavily in training and mentorship, which is incredibly helpful especially if you're just starting out.  
</p>
<p begin="69">They also do a lot to support you as you're connecting both within the bank and with your clients so you can really develop that part of your career.  
</p>
<p begin="78" end="93">And they also connect you with not just your group, but the bank more broadly here as well as around the globe.  So you can really help figure out what opportunity is best for you within this business as you develop through your career. 
</p>
<p begin="97">New York's a fantastic place to work. It's really the financial capital of North America, if not the world.  It gives you that opportunity to really be in the center of everything that's going on in financial markets,  
</p>
<p begin="110">and it gives you the opportunity, even if you're not working with everything directly, to be exposed to it and to really build your knowledge set. 
</p>
<p begin="118">When I'm not working here at Bank of America Merrill Lynch, I also work a lot on a not-for-profit I co-founded about four years ago called the Resolution Project.  
</p>
<p begin="127" end="133">We're a social venture incubator.  We help college students start not-for-profits that help effect change in their communities. 
</p>	 
<p begin="138">I think someone should choose Bank of America Merrill Lynch because of the culture here.   
</p>
<p begin="142">It's really a group of very smart, very driven individuals, who are really focused on doing what's best for the bank and doing what's best for its employees and really helping you develop. 
</p>
<p begin="157">You have the opportunity here to talk to so many different people in so many different parts of the sales and trading business and learn from their experiences.  
</p>
<p begin="166" end="180">And on top of that, the platform that Bank of America Merrill Lynch offers worldwide is incredible.  They give you the opportunity to find what's best for you and where you really want to make your career. 
</p>
			

		</div>    
	</body>
</tt>