<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt>
	<head>
		<styling>
		</styling>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div xml:lang="en">
<p begin="10">My name is Kevin.  I’m in the Consumer MBA Program and currently I’m a Product Manager for Emerging Payments. 
</p>	
<p begin="16">On a day-to-day basis, product management is about influencing others and making sure that you see the bigger picture – that you have the vision and can articulate that and really get everyone on your team.  
</p>
<p begin="28" end="39">I use my skills from finance, my skills from marketing, my skills from operations, on a daily basis.  But the most important skills for me are organizational behavior and communication.  
</p>
<p begin="43">I came to the bank through one of the different diversity hire channels.  I came through Reaching Out, the LGBT MBA Conference, and I felt included from day one.  
</p>
<p begin="52" end="60">I felt like I added something different to the bank and that I could be who I wanted to be and that the bank embraced that and sought me out because of it. 
</p>
<p begin="64">This is a bank that cares about its customers and it cares about its associates. And you need to show that you’ve done a little research.  
</p>
<p begin="72">Look at the core values; think about how we impact people on a daily basis.  
</p>
<p begin="77">But I would also say before your interview - know your story, know how you fit into Bank of America.  I think I’m not a traditional banking background – psychology and art history and I worked in a museum.  
</p>
<p begin="90" end="99">But I work with people every day that are nontraditional backgrounds.  There is no one right banker at Bank of America.  We want diversity. 
</p>
<p begin="103">Life is Charlotte is laid back but also exciting.  So you really have an opportunity to get involved anywhere you want.  I am the volunteer coordinator for our Carolinas LGBT Pride Network. 
</p>
<p begin="117" end="125">I’ve been able to get us out into the community, actually get the bank out interacting with people at food banks, at the AIDS Walk and at the upcoming Pride Festival. 
</p>
<p begin="128">Coming to Bank of America, it’s not just a job, it’s a great job. It’s professional and personal development.
</p>
<p begin="134">We have 60 million consumers out there that I can impact on a daily basis through product management, through working in this Consumer MBA Program.  
</p>
<p begin="143" end="147">It’s an amazing responsibility, and it makes me really identify with the work that I’m doing. 
</p>
			

		</div>    
	</body>
</tt>