<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt>
	<head>
		<styling>
		</styling>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div xml:lang="en">
<p begin="10">Hi.  I'm Zach.  I'm a treasury solutions analyst here with the Commercial Real Estate Banking group at Bank of America. 
</p>
<p begin="15">Here at the bank in the Commercial Real Estate Banking group, we offer two products to our clients.  We offer a credit product that allows clients to buy property.  
</p>
<p begin="27" end="34">And then, what I do is when we work with those credit clients to manage their cash and their liquidity for all commercial real estate banking. 
</p>
<p begin="37">The reason it’s exciting to work here at the bank for me is I had always been focused on real estate throughout my undergraduate career.  
</p>
<p begin="44" end="53">Here at the bank, I'm able to look at that from a completely new perspective and develop new skills and ideas that I have never really had before in my real estate background. 
</p>
<p begin="57">The people that have helped me along the way here at the bank were my manager and my mentor while I was first in the analyst program.  
</p>
<p begin="64">They took the time to learn who I am as a person and that really helped me develop my skills. 
</p>
<p begin="70">The group atmosphere here at the bank is great.  I really developed close relationships with all of the analysts in my program.  
</p>
<p begin="77" end="85">And even though we're out of the program now, I still talk to them to this day to develop not just my knowledge but friendships and networking opportunities as well. 
</p>
<p begin="90">Bank of America is a great place to give someone right out of undergraduate an opportunity to grow into a career and not just a job.  
</p>
<p begin="97" end="112">The bank, in general, really provides opportunities for all kinds of individuals in all facets of business to grow and develop skill sets needed to not just function in a job environment, but develop and build a successful career as well. 
</p>	
<p begin="116">The advice that I could give to an undergraduate interested in the commercial real estate banking program is to think of this as a way to develop your career.  
</p>
<p begin="124">Not just as a job out of college.  Because that’s what this opportunity is.  It’s a very unique, exciting opportunity that gives you ways to grow and succeed in commercial real estate that not a lot of other places are able to do. 
</p>
<p begin="137" end="143">There’s so many different opportunities and jobs that you can take here at the bank that it’s really the sky is the limit. 
</p>
	

		</div>    
	</body>
</tt>