<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt>
	<head>
		<styling>
		</styling>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div xml:lang="en">
<p begin="00" end="04">I’m Jeff Rosenstock and I’ve got the privilege of running Queens Theatre in the Park.  
</p>
<p begin="10">Our role really in working with the corporate sector is to identify potential corporate partners who understand that building a strong community is building strong business. 
</p>
<p begin="15" end="23">I hope through our theatre that we have these partnerships over the long-term and ultimately really impact a lot of people by doing that.
</p>
<p begin="28">Queens Theatre in the Park has been a destination in Queens always and now that it’s expanded, obviously it’s brought new talent.  
</p>
<p begin="30" end="39">Before people came in, saw performance and then maybe went to Manhattan or to another borough where they came from to have a meal.  Now Queens Theatre in the Park is having them stay in Queens.
</p>
<p begin="43">We rely on all little different pieces of the puzzle.  Queens Theatre in the Park is very important to us.  We regularly do catering jobs for them.  To have a partner like Jeff in Queens Theatre here, it’s tremendous.  
</p>
<p begin="52">We really are thankful that we get recommendations from the theatre.  They leave here happy, they’ll enjoy the show and it works on the other end also, sometimes they come after the show.  Everything works hand in hand.
</p>
<p begin="62" end="71">I’ve been working with William Charles Printing for 21 years and we really depend upon a vendor like a printer.
</p>
<p begin="74">Business is hard to find.  People aren’t spending money like they used to.  So, when you get somebody who appreciates what you’re doing, you want to continue with that.  You can’t take anything for granted.
</p>
<p begin="80" end="89">Linda DeSabato of Vallo Transportation and her company transports literally thousands of kids to attend performances at our theatre.
</p>
<p begin="93">I love working with Jeff.  It’s not like he’s renting a bus, it’s like we’re putting on a show.  The kids that we transport are really always so excited to go to the theatre.  
</p>
<p begin="97">They’re not just going to the Queens Theatre in the Park, they think they’re going straight to Broadway.  And, they are.  Our little Broadway.
</p>
<p begin="103" end="118">During tough times you really look and say, ‘How do we all stay in this business together.’  And, that’s not just the staff.  That’s the community that’s supporting us, that’s the community that knows who we are and that understands the value that we have in working together.
</p>

		</div>    
	</body>
</tt>