<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt>
	<head>
		<styling>
		</styling>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div xml:lang="en">
<p begin="10">Hi, I’m Saumya.  I work for the Oil and Gas Research Team.  I’m an associate with them.  
</p>
<p begin="14">I started in an oil and gas company.  So I was engineer.  They recruited me.  I worked in Egypt for a couple of years and then 
</p>
<p begin="21">I went to MBA at NYU Stern and from there I was recruited here for the summer. And the rest is history.  
</p>
<p begin="33">What an equity research analyst does is analyze the companies that they cover and help investors make a decision if they want to invest in them, hold them or sell them.  
</p>
<p begin="43">The best part of my job is the people that I work with.  They are the smartest, the best at their job.  But yet so humble, so helpful that you learn so much without being intimidated.   
</p>
<p begin="58">What I liked about my summer internship was the exposure that I got to different parts of the bank and how nice people were when you come in as an intern.  
</p>
<p begin="67">Their expectation - they have the right expectations from you.  They exactly know what they want out of you.  They’ve prepared for you so it obviously makes it an easier process to blend in.    
</p>
<p begin="75">I would definitely recommend summer internships to people only because if you’re undecided about groups or if you’re undecided about which bank to work in, it’s very important to work in the industry.  
</p>
<p begin="86">Work with people and realize what is expected out of people, what are the challenges, what are the talents or skills required.  It’s very important.  
</p>
<p begin="100">The way the bank promotes opportunities is like the women’s groups that they have.  They call you for lunches, make you meet senior women.  
</p>
<p begin="107">They organize these MBA events where you go meet other MBAs and MDs and VPs and directors.  So it just increases your network.  
</p>
<p begin="118">The best part about living in London is the work/life balance you get.  People respect the fact that you have weekends.  It rains a lot; you don’t even have to go out.  It’s a lot of fun.  
</p>
<p begin="134">People should come to Bank of America because of:  A. the brand name that it is and, B. the platform that it gives them.  You cover all the asset classes.  
</p>
<p begin="143">You have so many opportunities even later on to move within assets and within countries.  So, just for the opportunities and the brand.  

   
</p>
			

		</div>    
	</body>
</tt>